Pepe Doval

Cell: +34-650-795-886 Email: pepellou@gmail.com

I am a senior software developer with 10+ years of experience, seeking for new places to develop my craft. I'm an advocate for agile methodologies and Software Craftsmanship, as well as a very active member of the Spanish agile community. Despite my leadership skills, my passion is coding.



Education

University of Vigo

Major: Computer Science Engineering

Minor: Physics

Predoctoral studies: Artificial Intelligence

Courses: Pedagogical skills, bioinformatics, graphic design, free software, web

frameworks, ...

Skills

Software sculpting skills

Unit testing, pair programming, agile methodologies, full stack.

Personal skills

Ethics, team leadership, professionalism.

Experience

Trabeculae E.B.T.

Head of IT/Developer - Ourense, Spain - 2008-2010

- Developed software for building three-dimensional models from bone microtomography
- · Designed and developed core internal software for the company
- Developed a software for medical follow-up of patients operated on hip

Agil-AZ

CEO/Developer - Santiago de Compostela - 2010-2014

- Run the company from scratch. Managed to hire a small team of developers :-)
- Developed 40+ software projects, mostly for startups
- Mostly web development; also mobile apps and backend
- · Explored and perfected the use of different methodologies

Hermanos Karapatrov

Software Sculptor - Milladoiro - 2011-2013

- Contributed to 10+ audiovisual projects
- Mostly real time image processing; also some web development and graphic design

SetPay

Full Stack Developer - Santiago de Compostela - 2014-2017

- Contributed to development of front-end and back-end of the core products
- Trained other developers
- · Methodology leader
- · Mostly bank software, Java technologies and Angular

NoLegalTech

The Tech Guy - Milladoiro - 2018-today

- To the eyes of our customers, I do magic to create what they want from their ideas
- · I also extinguish tech fires
- Mostly web development (full stack)

Hobbies

Chess, Maths, Books Hackathons and Coding Dojos

Languages

Native: Galician, Spanish

Fluent: English

Studied: French, German, Italian, Portuguese, Russian